<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-16"?>
<string_tips>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999001</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC001</name>
    <body>Tip: You do not lose Experience Points when you are killed by a player in the Arena or PvP.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999002</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC002</name>
    <body>Lore: Lady Siel was the Empyrean Lord of Time. When the Tower shattered,\nSiel gave her life force to prevent the hollow sphere of Atreia from scattering into space.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999003</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC003</name>
    <body>Hint: New skills can be learned automatically depending on your level.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999004</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC004</name>
    <body>Tip: Access Help by pressing the &lt;H&gt; key.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999005</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC005</name>
    <body>Hint: From Level 50 onwards, you will lose XP if you die.\nSome of the lost XP can be restored by the soul healer next to the Obelisks.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999006</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC006</name>
    <body>Tip: To change where you resurrect when you die, bind to an Obelisk.\nTo find nearby Obelisks type "/where obelisk".</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999007</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC007</name>
    <body>Tip: The Abyss is a PvPvE area available to characters of Level 25 and higher.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999008</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC008</name>
    <body>Tip: To link information on an item, quest, or skill in Chat, Ctrl-Right-Click the item.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999009</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC009</name>
    <body>Lore: Lady Ariel leads the Seraphim Lords. Before the Cataclysm,\nAriel supported Israphel's call for peace. Now, the Lady of Light watches over Elysea.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999010</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC010</name>
    <body>Lore: Lord Azphel opposed peace with the Balaur.\nAs Lord of Shadows, he leads the Shedim Lords protecting Asmodae.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999011</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC011</name>
    <body>Tip: To view their class, level, and other information, Click the names of other characters in chat.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999012</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC012</name>
    <body>Tip: To see how items would look on your character, Ctrl-Click the item.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999013</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC013</name>
    <body>Lore: Devotees of Lady Yustiel, the Seraphim Lord of Life, work tirelessly\nhoping to restore Eltnen to its former glory as the breadbasket of Elysea.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999014</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC014</name>
    <body>Tip: Toggle auto-run by pressing &lt;NumLock&gt;.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999015</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC015</name>
    <body>Lore: The Empyrean Lord of Space, Israphel, argued for peace talks with the Balaur.\nWhen the Empyrean Lords met with the Dragon Lords, the ensuing Cataclysm destroyed Lord Israphel, Lady Siel, and the Tower.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999016</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC016</name>
    <body>Tip: Cities and many towns have mailboxes where you can send and receive mail.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999017</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC017</name>
    <body>Tip: Falling from a great height will cause you to suffer damage, or even to die.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999018</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC018</name>
    <body>Tip: You can ascend as a Daeva and choose a sub-class when you reach Level 10.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999019</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC019</name>
    <body>Tip: The green gauge around the Fly button (wings icon) displays your remaining flying time.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999020</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC020</name>
    <body>Tip: Daevas can glide by pressing the &lt;Space Bar&gt; in the middle of a jump.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999021</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC021</name>
    <body>Tip: Zones that are extremely populated may have more than one zone channel. Group members need to be in the same channel.\nChange your channel number in Menu/Support/Change Channel.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999022</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC022</name>
    <body>Tip: The Fly button (wings icon) toggles flight. Mousing over it shows flight controls,\nremaining fly time, or how long until you can unfurl your wings again.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999023</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC023</name>
    <body>Tip: Aggressive monsters and characters of the opposing faction are displayed as red dots on the Compass.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999024</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC024</name>
    <body>Tip: Whisper back to the last person who sent you a Whisper by pressing &lt;T&gt;.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999025</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC025</name>
    <body>Tip: Check the box in the Quest Window to load a quest to the Quest Tracker.\nQuest Tracker allows you to monitor your quest progress from the User Interface while playing.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999026</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC026</name>
    <body>Tip: Click blue words in quests to bring up a dictionary definition with more detailed information.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999027</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC027</name>
    <body>Tip: The Menu button at the bottom of the screen offers access to many useful windows.\nDefault &lt;F10&gt; key for Menu.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999028</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC028</name>
    <body>Tip: Group Leaders can display brands on targets by right-clicking the Target, by typing "/Brand #" in chat,\nor by right-clicking the Show Brand Action in the Skills window.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999029</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC029</name>
    <body>Tip: You can press 'B' to activate or deactivate the equipped Shards.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999030</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC030</name>
    <body>Tip: Find NPCs or locations by typing "/where CharacterName" in chat.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999031</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC031</name>
    <body>Tip: To view both the map and the game screen at the same time, use the transparent overlay.\nDefault &lt;N&gt; key.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999032</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC032</name>
    <body>Tip: To mark locations on your map and link to them in chat, Ctrl-Right-Click on the map.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999033</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC033</name>
    <body>Tip: Right-Clicking a location mark you've made on the map opens a pop-up menu with additional features.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999034</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC034</name>
    <body>Lore: Lord Israphel was the Empyrean Lord of Space.\nHe lost his life, along with Lady Siel, when the Tower shattered.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999035</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC035</name>
    <body>Tip: When your craft skill is maxed out for your skill level, talk to a crafting master to access the next level.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999036</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC036</name>
    <body>Tip: To view current Legion or Character rankings, first click the Influence Ratio icon on the bottom right of the screen, then the Abyss Rank button.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999037</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC037</name>
    <body>Tip: Legions can only be created or disbanded by visiting the Legions Board in Pandaemonium or Sanctum.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999038</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC038</name>
    <body>Tip: Moving during combat can increase your defence or attack.\nOn-screen arrows indicate the current active bonuses.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999039</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC039</name>
    <body>Tip: Up to three additional Quickbars, as well as a floating Quickbar, are available in Game Options.\nDefault &lt;O&gt; key for Options.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999040</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC040</name>
    <body>Tip: Fortresses and cities have warehouses where you can store spare items.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999041</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC041</name>
    <body>Tip: All characters from one account share an account warehouse.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999042</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC042</name>
    <body>Tip: Expand your Cube (inventory) space by visiting a cube artisan.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999043</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED001</name>
    <body>Tip: Rifts are corridors to enemy territory. There is a limit on the number of characters who can travel through a rift.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999044</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED002</name>
    <body>Tip: Toggle the altitude lock while flying by pressing Scroll Lock.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999045</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED003</name>
    <body>Tip: To copy character, item, or location information from chat to your Memo Pad, Right-Click the information.\nNavigate to your Memo Pad through Menu/Community.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999046</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED004</name>
    <body>Tip: Capturing a fortress in the Abyss temporarily boosts the abilities of all members of the conquering faction.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999047</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED005</name>
    <body>Tip: Significant differences in Influence will give a PvP boost to the disadvantaged faction.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999048</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED006</name>
    <body>Tip: Fortresses and cities have Abyss Distributors where you can spend Abyss Points on armour and weapons.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999049</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED007</name>
    <body>Tip: You can consume food and beverages at the same time.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999050</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED008</name>
    <body>Tip: At Level 20, you can take quests to become qualified to equip Stigma Stones.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999051</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED009</name>
    <body>Hint: An item's rank is displayed as follows – white for Normal, green for Superior, blue for Heroic, yellow for Fabled, orange for Eternal and violet for Mythical.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999052</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED010</name>
    <body>Tip: You can use this to change the appearance of an item in the Modify Appearance menu under [Boost/Modify].</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999053</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED011</name>
    <body>Tip: Enhancing your weapon with Godstones requires a visit to a Godstone Socketer in the city.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999054</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED012</name>
    <body>Lore: The Seraphim Lord Nezekan carries Izith, the shield of mystery. He is known for his fair yet swift Justice.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999055</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED013</name>
    <body>Tip: When a quest marker appears as a sunburst, that NPC has a reward waiting for you.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999056</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED014</name>
    <body>Tip: To toggle the camera view to face your character, click the scroll wheel.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999057</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED015</name>
    <body>Tip: You can equip two weapon sets.\nDefault &lt;Shift-Z&gt; to switch between them.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999058</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED016</name>
    <body>Lore: Zikel demonstrated his title as the Shedim Lord of Destruction when the Elyos Storm Legion attacked Asmodae.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999059</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED017</name>
    <body>Tip: You don't have to get to a mailbox to read Express Mail.\nJust click the Express Package Icon next to your Compass.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999060</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED018</name>
    <body>Lore: Favoured by Asmodian Assassins, Lady Triniel is dispassionate\nand unsurprisingly, as the Shedim Lord of Death, fatal.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999061</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED019</name>
    <body>Tip: Cycle through nearby targets by pressing &lt;Tab&gt;.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999062</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED020</name>
    <body>Tip: The number of dots on the left of the Target Window indicates the difficulty of the monster.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999063</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED021</name>
    <body>Tip: Some hard-to-find NPCs wander about, rather than remaining in one spot.\nAlso, some hard-to-find NPCs only appear at specific times.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999064</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED022</name>
    <body>Tip: View the current status of the Abyss War by selecting the Abyss on the map.\nDefault &lt;M&gt; key for the Map.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999065</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED023</name>
    <body>Tip: When a Legion reaches Level 3, they can design and register their own Legion emblem.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999066</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED024</name>
    <body>Tip: DP does not reset until the character has been logged off for 5 minutes.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999067</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED025</name>
    <body>Tip: Well-timed attacks can interrupt an enemy's skills or spells.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999068</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED026</name>
    <body>Tip: Altered States may cause you to become temporarily immobilized or unable to fight.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999069</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED027</name>
    <body>Tip: Altered States such as Bleeding or Poisoned will cause you to suffer periodic damage.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999070</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED028</name>
    <body>Lore: Vaizel, Lord of Freedom, is said to spend more time with Humans than the other Seraphim Lords.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999071</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED029</name>
    <body>Tip: Spiritmasters can issue commands to spirits by using the Command buttons next to the Quickbar.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999072</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED030</name>
    <body>Tip: When you use an item to transform into an animal, you will usually not be able to use any skills.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999073</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED031</name>
    <body>Tip: Dredgions are more likely to take interest in the faction with the higher Influence Ratio.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999074</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED032</name>
    <body>Tip: Artefacts play an important strategic role in Fortress Battles.\nYou can see who possesses an Artefact on the Abyss map. Default &lt;M&gt; key for the Map.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999075</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED033</name>
    <body>Tip: You can earn Abyss Points with Fortress Battles, or by hunting monsters in the Abyss.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999076</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED034</name>
    <body>Lore: Lady Lumiel, Shedim Lord of Wisdom, insulted Lord Kaisinel hundreds of years ago.\nThe Seraphim Lord of Illusion still holds a grudge against her.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999077</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED035</name>
    <body>Tip: Teleporting is more expensive in the Abyss when a Fortress Battle is in progress there.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999078</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED036</name>
    <body>Lore: Shedim Lord Marchutan is the Asmodian Lord of Fate, and the Lord generally associated with Asmodian Chanters.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999079</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED037</name>
    <body>Tip: The Aetheric Field of a fortress protects it from attacks from above and below.\nThis protection is lost when the Aetheric Field Generator is destroyed.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999080</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED038</name>
    <body>Tip: Enchantment Stones, Manastones, and Godstones permanently enhance weapons or armour.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999081</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED039</name>
    <body>Tip: If you have armour or weapons you no longer want, you can create Enchantment Stones by using extraction tools.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999082</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED040</name>
    <body>Tip: You can extract high level Enchantment stones from high rank items.\nHigher level Enchantment stones have a higher success rate.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999083</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED041</name>
    <body>Tip: A failed enchantment attempt weakens previous enchantments on that item by 1 level.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999084</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED042</name>
    <body>Tip: To use a Godstone to strengthen an item, visit a Godstone Socketer.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999085</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED043</name>
    <body>Tip: Soul Bound items cannot be sold or traded to other characters, but can be sold to merchants.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999086</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED044</name>
    <body>Tip: To divide multiple items, Shift-Double-Click the item stack.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999087</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED045</name>
    <body>Tip: A critical success during crafting will result in a better crafted item, which will have better bonuses.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999088</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED046</name>
    <body>Tip: Increase your crafting skills faster by completing Work Orders.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999089</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED047</name>
    <body>Tip: Players can type "/dice" or "/roll" to make random decisions.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999090</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED048</name>
    <body>Tip: Group Leaders can choose to divide loot by having members roll dice or bid on items.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999091</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED049</name>
    <body>Tip: Grey items are junk, and only of value to merchants.\nSell all junk items at once by clicking &lt;Sell all Misc&gt; in the merchant's Sell Window.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999092</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED050</name>
    <body>Tip: Trade Brokers allow you to buy or sell items on consignment.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999093</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED051</name>
    <body>Tip: Once your Legion is Level 2 or higher, you can use the Legion Item Merchant.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999094</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED052</name>
    <body>Tip: You can attach items or Kinah to mail that you send.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999095</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED053</name>
    <body>Tip: When mail arrives for you, a letter icon will appear next to the Compass. To read regular mail, go to a mailbox.\nTo find the nearest mailbox type "/where mailbox" in chat.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999096</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED054</name>
    <body>Tip: Use the Auto Arrange Inventory button at the bottom of your Cube to sort items by type.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999097</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED055</name>
    <body>Tip: Being in water can prevent a Daeva from flying. Deep water can injure or kill characters.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999098</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED056</name>
    <body>Tip: Some foods, items, and potions increase the duration of your flying time.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999099</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED057</name>
    <body>Tip: You cannot use items while gliding.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999100</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED058</name>
    <body>Tip: Once you become a Daeva, you can use a teleporter to travel to other regions and cities.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999101</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED059</name>
    <body>Tip: You cannot use items while on a hoverstone.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999102</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED060</name>
    <body>Tip: Emotes can liven up your communication with other players.\nDefault &lt;K&gt; key for Skills and Actions.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999103</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED061</name>
    <body>Tip: Make your skills, actions, and items more accessible by dragging them to the Quickbars.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999104</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED062</name>
    <body>Tip: You can lock the Quickbar slots by clicking the Padlock icon at the left of the Quickbar.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999105</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED063</name>
    <body>Tip: The user interface can be toggled off for clean screenshots by pressing &lt;F12&gt;.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999106</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED064</name>
    <body>Tip: To hide all other players on the screen, toggle with &lt;Shift-F12&gt;.\nRemember to toggle it back on or enemy players will remain hidden from you.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999107</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED065</name>
    <body>Tip: When your icon on the Compass is magenta, you are at an altitude where you could die if you fall.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999108</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED066</name>
    <body>Tip: The &lt;Enter&gt; key opens the Chat Window.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999109</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED067</name>
    <body>Tip: Click and drag the Chat Window tabs to rearrange them, or to put them anywhere on the screen.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999110</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED068</name>
    <body>Tip: To send another Whisper to the same person you last sent a Whisper to, press &lt;Tab&gt; while in the Chat Window.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999111</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED069</name>
    <body>Tip: Video Tutorials are available in Beginner Help.\nDefault &lt;H&gt; key for Help.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999112</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED070</name>
    <body>Tip: You can see how your class skills chain together in the Chain tab of the Skill Window.\nDefault &lt;K&gt; key for Skills.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999113</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED071</name>
    <body>Tip: For easier contact, add friends to your Friends list.\nDefault &lt;V&gt; key for Social.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999114</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED072</name>
    <body>Tip: Display the distance to your target in the Combat Info section of Game Options.\nDefault &lt;O&gt; key for Options.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999115</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED073</name>
    <body>Tip: Set the User Interface to top or bottom in Game Options.\nDefault &lt;O&gt; key for Options.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999116</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED074</name>
    <body>Tip: Macros allow more convenient access to sequences of actions you perform frequently.\nDefault &lt;U&gt; key.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999117</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED075</name>
    <body>Tip: To auto-follow a targeted group member, Double-Click the Group Window.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999118</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED076</name>
    <body>Tip: Important hints for quests may appear in NPC dialogues and cutscenes.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999119</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED077</name>
    <body>Tip: Complete Coin Quests to earn more Coins, which can be exchanged for valuable rare rewards.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999120</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED078</name>
    <body>Tip: Certain monsters drop items that begin quests.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999121</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED079</name>
    <body>Tip: When a monster shouts for help during combat, its companions may join the fight.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999122</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED080</name>
    <body>Tip: Monsters with unique names are more powerful, and drop more valuable items.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999123</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED081</name>
    <body>Tip: NPC allies in enemy bases have more powerful stats and skills than normal monsters.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999124</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED082</name>
    <body>Tip: Treasure boxes don't always yield valuable items.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999125</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED083</name>
    <body>Tip: Some skills cannot be used while flying.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999126</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED084</name>
    <body>Tip: You cannot request a duel with a player who is in combat or trade.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999127</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED085</name>
    <body>Tip: In the Arena, all players outside your group count as enemies.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999128</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED086</name>
    <body>Tip: Prices and taxes fluctuate with your faction's Influence Ratio.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999129</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED087</name>
    <body>Tip: To know how much time, how many bindings, and how many resurrections remain on a Kisk,\nhover your cursor over the Kisk.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999130</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED088</name>
    <body>Tip: Many towns have a Manastone Remover who can remove Manastones from an item so you can add new ones.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999131</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED089</name>
    <body>Tip: To restore an item's original colour, buy Dye Remover from a city merchant .</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999132</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED090</name>
    <body>Tip: Vortices floating in the sky provide Aether for crafting.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999133</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED091</name>
    <body>Tip: You increase your Legion's level by earning Abyss Points.</body>
    <rank>3</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999134</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED092</name>
    <body>Tip: You can create a private chat channel for you and your friends.\nType "/channelhelp" to learn more.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999135</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED093</name>
    <body>Tip: Open a private store to sell things to other players.\nDefault &lt;Y&gt; key.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999136</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED094</name>
    <body>Tip: You cannot progress with some quests unless you are wearing a specific title.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999137</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED095</name>
    <body>Tip: The icon next to the Compass tells you the current time of day.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999138</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED096</name>
    <body>Tip: To know when you can capture a fortress or artefact, hover your cursor over its icon on the Abyss map.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999139</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED097</name>
    <body>Tip: You can reduce the size of the User Interface and windows in Game Options.\nDefault &lt;O&gt; key for Options.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999140</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED098</name>
    <body>Tip: Some merchant NPCs may only appear at certain times of day or during events.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999141</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED099</name>
    <body>Tip: Test your skills against other players by duelling.\nTo bring up the option to Request Duel, Right-click the player or type "/duel".</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999142</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED100</name>
    <body>Tip: You can enable viewing your target's target in the Combat Info section of the Game Options window.\nDefault &lt;O&gt; key for Options.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999143</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED101</name>
    <body>Tip: To send a whisper to someone, type "/w CharacterName Message" in chat.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999144</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC043</name>
    <body>Hint: Use the &lt;H&gt; button to open the help window, where you will find answers to your questions, along with information about the game.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999145</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC044</name>
    <body>Tip: Limited Sale Merchant NPCs indicated as [Sold Out] cannot sell particular items until their goods are restocked.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999146</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC045</name>
    <body>Tip: Items with a one-per-day limit can't be purchased if their daily limit has been reached, even if the Merchant NPC has not\nindicated it as [Sold Out]. Items will be available for purchase again at a specified time.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999147</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC046</name>
    <body>Tip: Items marked as "Bundled Material Items" can be split into 3 lower grade material items of the same type.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999148</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC047</name>
    <body>Tip: Fusing 2 two-handed weapons enhances its stats and increases its number of Manastone slots.\nYou can combine weapons by visiting the Armsfusion Officer at the remodel shops in large cities.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999149</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC048</name>
    <body>Tip: You can obtain a daily quest when you join a special organization. The daily quest is reset at 9:00 AM.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999150</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED127</name>
    <body>Hint: The insignias that you receive for completing daily quests can be exchanged for a variety of rewards.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999151</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED128</name>
    <body>Hint: A few merchants loan out items that may only be used for a certain length of time.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999152</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED129</name>
    <body>Hint: A borrowed item cannot be enhanced using Manastones or Enchantment Stones. It can also not be extracted or sold. It disappears automatically when its usage time expires.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999153</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC052</name>
    <body>Tip: Using a supplement increases the success rate of enchanting or Manastone socketing.\nSupplements can be purchased from Potion Suppliers in every village.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999154</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC053</name>
    <body>Tip: When enchanting, you must use a supplement that is appropriate for the level of the weapon.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999155</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC054</name>
    <body>Tip: You can travel to Balaurea at any time. Use the Aerolink in each city to do so.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999156</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC055</name>
    <body>Tip: Balaurea has windstreams, which enable you to travel to your destination faster.\nYou can catch a windstream by gliding into it.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999157</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC056</name>
    <body>Tip: You can find a group more easily by pressing the &lt;Shift+v&gt; keys or &lt;Start Menu - Find Group&gt; to open the Find Group window.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999158</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC057</name>
    <body>Tip: Using the info boards in a city allows you to locate an NPC easily.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999159</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC058</name>
    <body>Tip: You can find out the wait time remaining for instanced zones\nby using &lt;Start Menu - Instance Info&gt; or the "/CheckEntry" command.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999160</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC059</name>
    <body>Tip: You can still check your mail at the Mailbox even when the Express Courier is not there.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999161</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC060</name>
    <body>Tip: You can't receive new mail if your Mailbox is full.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999162</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC061</name>
    <body>Tip: When using a Trade Broker NPC, right-clicking on one of your items will automatically enter the search word on the Trade Broker window.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999163</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED130</name>
    <body>Hint: Once you have reached Level 10, you will be able to use the teleport statues in the towns to travel to the Temple of the Lord.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999164</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED102</name>
    <body>Tip: You may only join one organization at a time that gives daily quests.\nTo join another organization, you must leave the current one first.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999165</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED103</name>
    <body>Tip: While traveling on a windstream, you may end up exiting by attempting to change your direction or alter your speed.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999166</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED104</name>
    <body>Tip: When you defeat certain foes, an ascending air current or geyser may form nearby.\nYou can ride the geyser to a higher elevation by gliding above it.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999167</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC063</name>
    <body>Tip: When you become a Mentor, you can form a party with characters that are more than 10 levels lower than you.\nYou can't obtain EXP and items while you are Mentor.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999168</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED131</name>
    <body>Hint: Pets belonging to other characters will not be shown if you check the box marked 'Hide other players' Pets' under &lt;System settings - Player settings - User interface&gt;.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999169</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC065</name>
    <body>Hint: You can increase the resolution by checking the box marked 'High quality' under &lt;System settings - Graphics settings - Graphics engine&gt;.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999170</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED105</name>
    <body>Tip: The slayer penalty you received by killing the opposing race is not applicable to your ally's zone.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999171</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED106</name>
    <body>Tip: You cannot use certain skills or items while in some zones.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999172</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED107</name>
    <body>Tip: You can obtain special weapons and armour from Contributors in the Empyrean Crucible.\nThese items can be Conditioned, and is made stronger depending on its Conditioning level.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999173</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED108</name>
    <body>Tip: Pets may give you presents when they feel good.\nIf you want to make them feel good, summon them for longer hours or use the &lt;Pet Care&gt; command.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999174</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC066</name>
    <body>Hint: You cannot attack the opposing faction in a neutral zone.\nHowever, there are no restrictions in battle zones.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999175</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC067</name>
    <body>Tip: Watch your back in a disputed zone--your opponents may attack at any time.</body>
    <rank>3</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999176</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED109</name>
    <body>Tip: Balaurea Teleporters can only send you to other Balaurea locations.</body>
    <rank>3</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999177</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED110</name>
    <body>Tip: To board the warship, use the special teleport statue in Kamar.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999178</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC068</name>
    <body>Tip: To enter Tiamaranta's Eye, your race must control 2 or more Hearts of Tiamat's power.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999179</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC069</name>
    <body>Tip: If you occupy 3 or more Hearts of Tiamat's power, only your allies can enter Tiamaranta's Eye.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999180</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC070</name>
    <body>Tip: Tiamaranta's Eye is a disputed zone, where enemy players may attack.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999181</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED111</name>
    <body>Tip: Use a Relationship Crystal to visit a friend's house.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999182</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC071</name>
    <body>Hint: If you delete a cabinet, you cannot access the items in it until it has been restored.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999183</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC072</name>
    <body>Tip: Cabinets with the same name share items.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999184</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED112</name>
    <body>Tip: Each character can own no more than one house.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999185</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC073</name>
    <body>Tip: Characters Level 21 and higher are eligible for a quest to obtain a studio.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999186</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC074</name>
    <body>Tip: Housing auctions begin every Monday and end the following Sunday at noon.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999187</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED113</name>
    <body>Tip: To sell your house, you need to visit a Housing Auctioneer.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999188</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED114</name>
    <body>Tip: Once you buy a new house, all items inside your previous house will be transferred to the new one.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999189</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC075</name>
    <body>Tip: When you enter your house, click the house-shaped icon on the lower half of the screen to begin decorating.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999190</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED115</name>
    <body>Tip: Talk to the butler in your house to decorate the exterior of that house.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999191</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED116</name>
    <body>Tip: You can change the access authority or kick visitors out of your house through a butler.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999192</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED117</name>
    <body>Tip: The 'Homeward Bound' skill can be obtained by doing the introductory housing quest.\nGroup members can come through the portal with you to visit your home.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999193</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC076</name>
    <body>Tip: Select &lt;Start Menu-Move to Channel/Beginner Server-Move to Beginner Server&gt; to move to the beginner server.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999194</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED118</name>
    <body>Tip: The availability of items subject to the Abyss rank varies from the Abyss ranks.\nA change in the rank may disable the equip and use of the item you have been using.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999195</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC077</name>
    <body>Tip: Select &lt;Start Menu-Additional Functions-Aion Powerbook&gt; to use the Aion Powerbook the same way you use it from the homepage.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999196</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC078</name>
    <body>Tip: Click the 'Drawing Tool' on the lower side of the map window to write pictured memos on the map and share them with your party and Alliance members.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999197</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC079</name>
    <body>Tip: Go to &lt;System Preferences-Game Preferences-Name&gt; and select the 'Display Collection Item Names' to show the name of a collection item on the screen.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999198</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC080</name>
    <body>Tip: You can preview your appearance by pressing &lt;Ctrl + clicking&gt; the weapon, armour or wings.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999199</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC081</name>
    <body>Tip: You can change the location of a Transparent Map via the Move button on the upper side of the window.\nYou can also fix its position by clicking the Lock button on the left-hand side of the Quickbar.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999200</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED119</name>
    <body>Tip: Equipment crafted by a user has slightly better odds with enchantments than other equipment.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999201</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC049</name>
    <body>Hint: You can escape a situation in which you are stuck by entering the "/Quick Return" command.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999202</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC050</name>
    <body>Hint: Quest objects, coins and tickets are automatically stored in a special Cube. Click on the symbol below your inventory to open it.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999203</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED120</name>
    <body>Hint: If you travel to the enemy camp via Portal Rift, you will not be punished for killing enemies belonging to the opposing faction.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999204</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED121</name>
    <body>Hint: There is a special NPC who exchanges items that are not available to buy.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999205</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC051</name>
    <body>Hint: The prices for purchasing and selling items may vary, depending on the NPC.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999206</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED122</name>
    <body>Hint: If you use two Enchantment Stones as a fusion tool, there is a chance that you might receive a higher level Enchantment Stone.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999207</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED123</name>
    <body>Hint: Enhance a weapon with Idian to add extra endurance attributes.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999208</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED124</name>
    <body>Hint: You can extract more Enchantment Stones from items that have a high enchantment level.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999209</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC062</name>
    <body>Hint: Press and hold the &lt;Alt&gt; key and use the scroll wheel to browse through the information pages for equipment items.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999210</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC064</name>
    <body>Hint: Press and hold &lt;Alt&gt; and move the cursor over the magnifying glass symbol on an equipment item to view information about it.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999211</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED125</name>
    <body>Hint: The identification of equipment items generates additional random attributes.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999212</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED126</name>
    <body>Hint: Re-identifying equipment items generates additional random attributes.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999213</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC082</name>
    <body>Hint: Press &lt;Tab&gt; in the loot window to select the next item. Use the shortcut &lt;Attack/Conversation/Pick up Item (C)&gt; to pick up the selected item.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999214</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC083</name>
    <body>Info: You can turn off the enemy warning feature in &lt;Environment settings-Game settings-Pets&gt;.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999215</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED132</name>
    <body>Hint: Ranks are awarded on the basis of the amount of Honour Points - starting at 1 Star Officer and going upwards.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999216</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED133</name>
    <body>Hint: Honour Points are deducted every day from players holding the rank of "1 Star Officer" or higher.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999217</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED134</name>
    <body>Hint: If you wrap a non-tradeable item, you can trade it one time.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999218</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_ADVANCED135</name>
    <body>Hint: Merged two-handed weapons can be wrapped after a weapon is removed.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999219</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC084</name>
    <body>Tip: You can have the Master of Blessing bless your equipment to improve it. The items will retain their enhancements after the blessing.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999220</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC086</name>
    <body>Tip: To improve your equipment, enhance it with a blessing. The items will retain part of their enhancement levels as well as any socketed Godstones and Manastones after the blessing. Look for a Master of Blessing in the big cities.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999221</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_BASIC087</name>
    <body>Tip: Certain items can only be traded if the seller and buyer belong to the same Legion.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999226</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_ADVANCED001</name>
    <body>Tip: Legendary and Ultimate Enchantment Stones can also be purchased with Stellium using limited coupons.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999227</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_ADVANCED002</name>
    <body>Tip: The Abyss Rift which leads to Red Katalam opens at a random location in Lakrum and Dumaha each day between 9 AM and 5 PM.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999228</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_ADVANCED003</name>
    <body>Tip: The Fortress Battle takes place simultaneously in the Abyss Core, Lakrum and Dumaha every Friday and Sunday at 10 PM.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999229</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_ADVANCED004</name>
    <body>Tip: The Altar Siege Battle takes place in Dumaha daily at midday and 8:00 PM.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999230</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_ADVANCED005</name>
    <body>Tip: If the Dumaha Altar is captured with Apsu's Blessing, you may receive a different reward than usual.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999231</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC001</name>
    <body>Tip: There are different ways to obtain Genesis Crystals. However, the main source is the quests which you can receive after capturing the Artefact Garrison in Lakrum.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999232</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC002</name>
    <body>Tip: In an extended battle, press SHIFT+F12 to activate minimal mode and improve game performance.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999233</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC003</name>
    <body>Tip: Repeatable quests which you receive when first playing an instance can be carried out twice a week. You will receive Enchantment Stones as a reward.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999234</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC004</name>
    <body>Tip: In the Orbis Training Arena in the Stellusia Underground you can enjoy PvP without any restrictions (like Soul Sickness).</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999235</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC005</name>
    <body>Tip: In Red Katalam, boxes show up in several places on the field which can be opened with keys for Legion boxes.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999236</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC006</name>
    <body>Tip: The 3 vs 3 Transformation Battlefield Illumiel can be entered every day between 11 AM and 3 PM and between 7 PM and 3 AM.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999237</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC007</name>
    <body>Tip: You can enter the Tower of Challenge through the lobby of the Empyrean Crucible.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999238</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_ADVANCED006</name>
    <body>Tip: The Item manual in the bottom part of your profile shows you your most valuable item and where you got it.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999239</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_ADVANCED007</name>
    <body>Tip: If you don't know what to do after level 76, press J to carry out Helper campaigns.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999240</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_ADVANCED008</name>
    <body>Tip: You can give Genesis Crystals to Genesis Crystal Traders in the major cities in Lakrum in return for equipment and Ancient Enchantment Stones.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999241</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_ADVANCED009</name>
    <body>Tip: Slot Stones are used to expand Manastone Slots. Fighting Spirit Fragments are used as upgrade material for upgrades.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999242</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC008</name>
    <body>Tip: Fusing 2 two-handed weapons improves the values and increases the number of Manastone Slots.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999243</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC009</name>
    <body>Tip: You can receive Slot Stones by extracting PvE equipment. You can receive Slot Stones and Fighting Spirit Fragments by extracting PvP equipment.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999244</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC010</name>
    <body>Tip: Press SHIFT+P to access magical crafting.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999245</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC011</name>
    <body>Tip: To link information on an item in a Chat, Ctrl-Right-Click the item.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999246</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC012</name>
    <body>Tip: To upgrade legendary equipment, you need ancient equipment with Enchantment Level +15 with all Manastone Slots activated.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999247</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC013</name>
    <body>Tip: Re-identification provides new option types and values, whereas Selection Re-identification only renews the values of the selected options.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999248</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC014</name>
    <body>Tip: Modify Appearance allows appearance skills to be applied to other equipment and used.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999249</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_ADVANCED010</name>
    <body>Tip: You receive additional effects in battle depending on the direction you move in. You can activate these combat movement buffs with the arrow on the screen.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999250</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_ADVANCED011</name>
    <body>Tip: Attributes obtained by Transformation Collection are applied to your character cumulatively.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999251</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_ADVANCED012</name>
    <body>Tip: Only the highest-level Collection skill is displayed.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999252</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_ADVANCED013</name>
    <body>Tip: 'Improved Daevanion Skill' can be boosted up to level 15.</body>
    <rank>1</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999253</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC015</name>
    <body>Tip: Use Custom Skill Chains to deploy multiple skills in a row with one key.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999254</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC016</name>
    <body>Tip: If you successfully combine 4 minions with evolution level 4, you receive one random minion of a higher level.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999255</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC017</name>
    <body>Tip: When your icon on the Compass is red, you are at an altitude where you could die if you fall.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999256</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC018</name>
    <body>Tip: Daevanion Skill Books let you learn Daevanion Skills with far more powerful effects than your previous skills.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999257</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC019</name>
    <body>Tip: You can escape a situation in which you are stuck by entering the command '/Quick Return'.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999258</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC020</name>
    <body>Tip: Click on 'Drawing Tools' in the bottom right of the map to make notes and then share these with your companions.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999259</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC021</name>
    <body>Tip: Press N to activate the transparent world map. This lets you view the map and the game screen at the same time.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999260</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC022</name>
    <body>Tip: Enter /PathFinding NPC Name to locate NPCs.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
  <string_tip>
    <id>999261</id>
    <name>STR_TIP_CHAT_BASIC023</name>
    <body>Tip: Click on Inventory shop in the bottom part of the inventory to sell items without having to see an NPC.</body>
    <rank>2</rank>
    <message_type>chat</message_type>
  </string_tip>
</string_tips>